VICTOR RUTSKIN

Full Stack Developer

Personal info

- ✓ Lashaka666@gmail.com
- **J** 052-3163179
- Yavne, Israel

Links

- **G** Github
- in Linkedin
- References
- Certificates

Skills

- ★ Software & Web Development
- Object Oriented Programming
- ★ Web API Integration
- ★ Micro-Service Architecture
- Relational Databases
- 🖈 🛮 Web Application Cyber Security
- ★ Scripting

Technologies

Frontend

- Javascript, HTML & CSS
- Angular
- Typescript
- B Rootstran

Backend

- </>/> C#
- .NET Core & Framework
- Python
- Microsoft SQL server (MSSQL)

Other

- git Git
- Electronic Warfare, Cyber RF, etc..
- Photoshop
- Burpsuite

Hobbies

- Gamino
- **1** Cooking
- @ Martial Arts

Languages

Hebrew
English

Russian



ABOUT ME

I am a tech enthusiast with a keen interest in programming and cybersecurity.

In the course of my professional journey, I have primarily focused on developing web APIs using .NET Core and Angular-based web applications.

Beyond coding, I enjoy experimenting with gadgets and keeping myself updated on cutting-edge technologies.

My knowledge extends to web application security practices, adding an extra layer of expertise to my skill set.

Employment History

Full Stack Developer, Albar

APR 2023 - PRESENT

· Credit Score Evaluation System

- I had a critical role in a large project that Evaluated customers' credit scores for loan eligibility.
- Collaborated with multiple companies through Web API and Web Service communication.
- Handled sensitive information.

· Project Management Web Application

- Independently developed.
- Utilized by the Dev team for deployment processes.
- Highly interactive and functional.

· Smart Form Project

- Created a smart form project for efficient form generation.
- Improved maintainability and accelerated deployment of new forms.

· Responsive Website Enhancement

- Transformed a single-screen-sized website into a responsive one.
- Enhanced interactivity and wrote a more efficient code base.

Legacy Project Maintenance and Microservices Transition

- Maintained and recreated legacy projects in a microservices architecture.
- Fearlessly handled complex tasks and turned the unknown into the known.

Electronic Warfare & Cyber Operator, IL Air Force

OCT 2019 - JUN 2022

- Operated multiple electronic warfare systems, for attack & defence purposes under intense pressure for more than 5000 Operational shift hours.
- Wide knowledge about ECM (Electronic countermeasure) & CRF (Cyber Over RF).
- Led a team as an Instruction Team Leader, and had more than 300 hours of soldier instruction, training & teaching.
- 03 Combatant Status.

Education

Software Development Course, Sela College

Jun 2022 - Apr 2023

- Intensive Program of 10 Months that covers the following areas
 - Object Oriented Programming using C.
 - Data Structures.
 - Algorithms and Complexity.
 - Javascript, HTML CSS.
 - .NET Framework Core, ASP.NET Core MVC , WPF Winforms.
 - Angular.
 - React.
 - NodeJS.
 - Sql.
 - Azure.
 - Git.

Tihon Hadash Tel-Aviv

2016 - 2019

Courses

The Complete Cyber Security Course: Hackers Exposed! By Nathan House, Udemy

Basic & Advanced Electronic Warfare Courses, IL Air Force

Advanced Soldier Instructing & Training Course, IL Air Force

VICTOR RUTSKIN

Full Stack Developer

Personal info

- ✓ Lashaka666@gmail.com
- 052-3163179
- Yavne, Israel

Links

- Github
- in Linkedin
- References
- Certificates

Skills

- ★ Software & Web Development
- ☆ Object Oriented Programming
- ★ Web API Integration
- ★ Micro-Service Architecture
- Relational Databases
- ★ Web Application Cyber Security
- ★ Scripting

Technologies

Frontend

- Javascript, HTML & CSS
- Angular
- Typescript
- B Bootstrap

Backend

- **\/>** C#
- .NET Core & Framework
- Python
- Microsoft SQL server (MSSQL)

Other

- git Git
- Electronic Warfare, Cyber RF, etc..
- Photoshop
- Burpsuite

Hobbies

- Gaming
- **11** Cooking
- 3 Martial Arts

Languages

Hebrew

English

****0

Page 2 of 2